[
 {
  "Date": 1,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "What is Serena Williams sister's first name?",
  "Answer": "Venus",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Paella is a famous dish for what countries' cuisine?",
  "Answer": "Spain",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "The larvae stage of a frog is called what?",
  "Answer": "Tadpole",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Finish these Katy Perry lyrics: \"I kissed a _____ and I liked it\"",
  "Answer": "Girl",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "In \"Wonder Woman\" (2017), who plays Diana Prince?",
  "Answer": "Gal Gadot",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 2,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Simone Biles grew up in what state?",
  "Answer": "Texas",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "New Mexico, Arizona, Texas and what other U.S. State all border Mexico?",
  "Answer": "California",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "A komodo dragon is what kind of animal?",
  "Answer": "Lizard",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "What is the oldest musical instrument in use today?",
  "Answer": "Flute",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "In the 2021 movie \"Dune\", Timothee Chalemet plays _____ Atreidis.",
  "Answer": "Paul",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 3,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Carmelo Anthony was drafted as the 3rd overall pick to the NBA. In this draft, who was the first overall pick?",
  "Answer": "LeBron James",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "After Rhode Island, which U.S. State is the smallest by land area?",
  "Answer": "Delaware",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What stock exchange is Google traded on?",
  "Answer": "NASDAQ",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Aretha Franklin is the \"Queen of ____\"?",
  "Answer": "Soul",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "In the 2015 \"Rocky\" spinoff movie, who plays Adonis Creed?",
  "Answer": "Michael B. Jordan",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 4,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Daniel \"Rudy\" Ruettiger played football for what Division 1 University?",
  "Answer": "Notre Dame",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What United States International Airport is rumored to feature tunnels below the airport built by the New World Order?",
  "Answer": "Denver",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "How many total pieces are played with in Chess?",
  "Answer": "32",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "\"U.N.I.T.Y\" was performed by what female hip hop artist?",
  "Answer": "Queen Latifah",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Adam Sandler, Jennifer Anniston, and Brooklyn Decker star in what 2011 film?",
  "Answer": "Just Go With It",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 5,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "What is Earvin Johnson Jr. nickname?",
  "Answer": "Magic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What is the most densely populated country in the world?",
  "Answer": "Bangladesh",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Which natural disaster is measured with the Richter Scale?",
  "Answer": "Earthquakes",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "What rapper spent three years in 9th grade?",
  "Answer": "Eminem",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Who stars in the 1983 movie \"Scarface\"?",
  "Answer": "Al Pacino",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 6,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Steve Nash won his MVPs on what NBA team?",
  "Answer": "Suns",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Italy borders San Marino, Slovenia, France, Switzerland, Austria, and what other country?",
  "Answer": "Vatican City",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What animals are pearls found in?",
  "Answer": "Oysters",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "The \"British Invasion\" started in what decade?",
  "Answer": "1960s",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Rosamund Pike and Ben Affleck star in what 2014 film?",
  "Answer": "Gone Girl",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 7,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Although finishing his career with the Arizona Cardinals, Emmitt Smith started his career for which NFL team?",
  "Answer": "Cowboys",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "The Tasmanian Devil is native to what country?",
  "Answer": "Australia",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "This Ford model was named after a fighter plane from World War II.",
  "Answer": "Mustang",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Made of rhinestone, this piece of clothing of Michael Jackson was auctioned off for $350,000.",
  "Answer": "Glove",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "In \"Inside Out\" (2015), Phyllis Smith plays what emotion?",
  "Answer": "Sadness",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 1,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "What is Serena Williams sister's first name?",
  "Answer": "Venus",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Paella is a famous dish for what countries' cuisine?",
  "Answer": "Spain",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "The larvae stage of a frog is called what?",
  "Answer": "Tadpole",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Finish these Katy Perry lyrics: \"I kissed a _____ and I liked it\"",
  "Answer": "Girl",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "In \"Wonder Woman\" (2017), who plays Diana Prince?",
  "Answer": "Gal Gadot",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 8,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Who is the all time leading goal scorer for the NHL?",
  "Answer": "Wayne Gretzky",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Paraguay and what other country are the two landlocked countries in South America?",
  "Answer": "Bolivia",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What liquor is made from a cactus?",
  "Answer": "Tequila",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "In what state is the \"birthplace of Jazz?\"",
  "Answer": "Louisiana",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What 2006 film stars Anne Hathaway and Meryl Streep?",
  "Answer": "The Devil Wears Prada",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 9,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Known mostly for his first name of \"Ichiro\", what was this Japanese outfielder's last name?",
  "Answer": "Suzuki",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What European Country has bomb shelters to accomadate every citizen?",
  "Answer": "Switzerland",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Starting in 1989, what American reality TV show is the longest running?",
  "Answer": "Cops",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "\"Umbrella\", \"Big Girls Don't Cry\", and \"Beautiful Girls\" were all released in what year?",
  "Answer": "2007",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Name the last movie released by Christopher Nolan:",
  "Answer": "Tenet",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 10,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "How many teams make it to March Madness?",
  "Answer": "68",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What year did Germany invade Poland to kickstart World War II",
  "Answer": "1939",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Sheryl Sandberg is currently the COO of what major tech company?",
  "Answer": "Facebook",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Steven Tyler is the lead singer for what Rock Band?",
  "Answer": "Aerosmith",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "\"Ben Affleck\", \"Jonn Hamm\", and \"Rebecca Hall\" star in what Boston based heist movie?",
  "Answer": "The Town",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 11,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "What country is reigning NBA MVP Nikola Jokic from?",
  "Answer": "Serbia",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What is the biggest city in South America with over 13 Million People? (World Population Review)",
  "Answer": "Buenos Aires",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "How many Apollo Missions succesfully went to the moon? (Please put integer value, ex. put 1 instead of one)",
  "Answer": "6",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "What \"Zac Brown Band\" has the most streams?",
  "Answer": "Chicken Fried",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Who just got recently cast to star in the remake of \"White Men Can't Jump\"?",
  "Answer": "Jack Harlow",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 12,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Who performed at the Super Bowl halftime show in 2021?",
  "Answer": "The Weeknd",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Santiago is the capital of what South American Country?",
  "Answer": "Chile",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Alan Turing helped crack war codes for what country during WWII",
  "Answer": "England",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "\"Driver' Liscence\" was the most streamed song on Spotify in 2021. Who's song is it?",
  "Answer": "Olivia Rodrigo",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "Matt Damon, Ben Affleck, and Robin Williams all team up in what movie?",
  "Answer": "Good Will Hunting",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 13,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "What year did Anthony Davis lead Kentucky to a championship?",
  "Answer": "2012",
  "Column5": "Can you help me phrase this"
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What's the capital of the Dominican Republic?",
  "Answer": "Santo Domingo",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What is the name of the former host of the Bachelor franchise?",
  "Answer": "Chris Harrison",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "What band wrote the famous song \"Basket Case\"?",
  "Answer": "Green Day",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What city is the setting for the High School Musical series?",
  "Answer": "Albuquerque",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 14,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What is Kylie Jenner and Travis Scott's first child's name?",
  "Answer": "Stormi",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What actress starred in \"50 First Date\", \"Never Been Kissed\", and \"The Wedding Singer\"?",
  "Answer": "Drew Barrymore",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 15,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Which southern restaurant has its own index to help determine the severity of nearby storms?",
  "Answer": "Waffle House",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Who ranked #1 on Spotify's top 50 female artists of 2021?",
  "Answer": "Taylor Swift",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What coming of age film did Matthew McConaughey first say his catch phrase \"alright, alright, alright\"?",
  "Answer": "Dazed and Confused",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
  {
  "Date": 16,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": "Because of the creators being on Spring Break in the:",
  "Answer": "Dominican Republic",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "We will not be able to create:",
  "Answer": "Questions",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "We are sorry for the:",
  "Answer": "inconvenience",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Questions will return on Monday the:",
  "Answer": "21st",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the Greatest Movie of all time?",
  "Answer": "Superbad",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 17,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Which musician is featured in season 2 of HBO's Euphoria?",
  "Answer": "Dominic Fike",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the capital city in the Wizard of Oz?",
  "Answer": "Emerald City",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 18,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "What country produces the most champagne in the world?",
  "Answer": "France",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "What podcast lovingly refers to their fans as armcherries?",
  "Answer": "Armchair Expert",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": "What is the name of Elle Woods chihuahua in the Legally Blonde movies?",
  "Answer": "Bruiser",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 19,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": "Which country was the first to allow women the right to vote?",
  "Answer": "New Zealand",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "Whose verse on Kanye West's \"Monster\" was almost cut because Kanye thought it was too good?",
  "Answer": "Nicki Minaj",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 20,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": "Which celebrity famously filed for divorce 72 days after getting married to an NBA star?",
  "Answer": "Kim Kardashian",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": "What podcast hosted by Cole Cuchna is known for throughly dissecting contemporary music albums?",
  "Answer": "Dissect",
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 21,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 22,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 23,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 24,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 25,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 26,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 27,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 28,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 29,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 30,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": 31,
  "Category": "Sports",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "World",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Anything",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Music",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 },
 {
  "Date": null,
  "Category": "Movies",
  "Question": null,
  "Answer": null,
  "Column5": null
 }
]
